Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Insurance and Benefits (1932-1968) (Box 59)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Switchmen's Union of North America miscellaneous insurance programs, 1962-1968 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, pamphlets
  - Insurance and Benefits: Various insurance companies' proposals to the Switchmen's Union of North America, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    A-1 - C-1. Pamphlets.
  - Insurance and Benefits: R. Hoffman case (benefit under Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act), 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    A-2 - B-2. Correspondence, manuscript.
- Insurance and Benefits: Health and Welfare, Union Labor Life; Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 1-3 (Box 60)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Proposed Health and Welfare Program, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Switchmen's Union of North America - notice to carriers regarding Health and Welfare Proposal, 1962-1963 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Correspondence with carriers on health and welfare, 1962-1964 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Health and welfare, insurance benefits, SUNA agreement, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Outline, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Pension Plans Disclosure Act (Welfare), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, pamphlets.
  - Insurance and Benefits: Health and Welfare pamphlets, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Health and Welfare memorandums, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Workbook material, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Manuscript, pamphlets
  - Insurance and Benefits: Correspondence on health and welfare, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Health and Welfare File, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    A-B. Correspondence, charts, etcetera.
  - Insurance and Benefits: News clippings on Insurance and Benefits, Health and Welfare, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Railway represented by Western Carriers Conference regarding health and welfare, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    A-1 - E-1. Manuscript.
  - Insurance and Benefits: Switchmen's Union of North America referendum - Health and Welfare Proposal, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Correspondence regarding Equitable Life Insurance Company on Health and Welfare, 1964-1967 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Insurance and Benefits: Union Labor Life Insurance, 1925-1926 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    A-D. Correspondence, manuscript.
  - Insurance and Benefits: Switchmen's Union of North America Union Labor Life insurance, 1932-1940 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    A-1 - F-1. Correspondence.
  - Insurance and Benefits: Switchmen's Union of North America Union Labor Life Insurance, 1941-1949 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    A-2 - C-2.
  - Insurance and Benefits: Switchmen's Union of North America Union Labor Life Insurance, 1950-1966 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 1), 1898 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    Manuscript, bound volume
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 2), 1899 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 3), 1900 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 4-8 (Box 61)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 4), 1901 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 5), 1902 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 6), 1903 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 7), 1904 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 8), 1905 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 9-14 (Box 62)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 9), 1906 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 10), 1907 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 11), 1908 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 12), 1909 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 13), 1910 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 14), 1912 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 15-20 (Box 63)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 15), 1915 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 16), 1914 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 17), 1915 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 18), 1916 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 19), 1917 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 20), 1918 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 21-26 (Box 64)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 21), 1919 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 22), 1920 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 23), 1921 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 24), 1922 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 25), 1923 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 26), 1924 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 27-32 (Box 65)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 27), 1925 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 28), 1926 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 29), 1927 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 30), 1928 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 31), 1929 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 32), 1930 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 33-38 (Box 66)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 33), 1931 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 34), 1932 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 35), 1933 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 36), 1934 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 37), 1935 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 38), 1936 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union Volumes 39-49, 45-48; miscellaneous material and publications (Box 67)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 39), 1937 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 40), 1938 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 41), 1939 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 42), 1940 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 43), 1941 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 44), 1942 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 45), 1943 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 46), 1944 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 47), 1945 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 48), 1946 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 49), 1947 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 45), 1948 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    Publisher restarted volume numbering at v.45. Manuscript, bound volume
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 46), 1949 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 47), 1950 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Journal of Switchmen's Union (Volume 48), 1951 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Material gathered for Switchmen's Union of North America Page (labor), 1962-1968 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, cartoons, broadsides, etcetera
  - Publications: Directory, 1952-1968 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Publications: Switchmen's Union of North America - Souvenir National Convention, 1897-1927 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    A-1 - C-1. Manuscript. 1897, 1909, 1915, 1927
  - Publications: The Switchmen's Light, 1961-1967 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    Manuscript. 1961-1963, 1967
- Miscellaneous Publications; Records of Local Lodges 1-51 (Box 68)
  - Publications: Switchmen's Union of North America ritual, 1951-1963 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Manuscript. 1951, 1963.
  - Publications: Official Year Book of Switchmen's Union of North America, 1943-1951 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Manuscript. 1943, 1951.
  - Publications: Broadsides (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Broadsides. No date.
  - Publications: Switchmen's Union of North America cartoons, 1936-1947 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Cartoons
  - Publications: Newspaper clippings, 1909-1968 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Newspaper clippings, 1909-1968 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Newspaper clippings, 1909-1968 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Newspaper clippings, 1909-1968 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Newspaper clippings, 1909-1968 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Newspaper clippings, 1909-1968 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 1 - Sample referendum ballot, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    Forms
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 2 - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 4 - Dispute within the Lodge, 1957-1960 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    A-B. Correspondence, ballots, miscellaneous. 1957, 1960.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 10 - Yearbook and Directory, 1919 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    3a. Manuscript.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 13 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1920-1938 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 13 - Seniority case of William Shultz, 1932-1933 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 13 - Case of G. Puchalsky, Thad Franks (disability benefits), 1935-1936 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 13 - Correspondence regarding lockers and shanties; question at Detroit, 1936 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 13 - Correspondence regarding Electing General Chairman from Detroit, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 14 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1921-1952 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    A-3 - C-3. Correspondence. 1921-1947, 1952
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 14 - 1933 Local Agreement (six day week); correspondence regarding local agreement at Toledo, 1940, 1933-1951 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    Involved in agreement(s): Switchmen's Union of North America, New York Central, Michigan Central, and Lodge 14. Correspondence. 1933, 1940-1951.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 14 - Correspondence regarding suspension of T.C. Griffith, 1935-1939 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 14 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1953-1968 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 29 - Correspondence regarding Assessments levied on Rock Island Railway, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 30 - Certification of membership for L.F. Patten, 1930-1943 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    Manuscript, correspondence. 1930, 1943
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 31 - Form letter from General Chairmen 31 Saint Paul Union Depot Company, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 35 (Also Lodges 17, 29, 36, 58, 199, 145) - Resolutions, 1901-1902 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 36 - Statement regarding strike called by Switchmen's Union of North America, 1916 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    Document
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 38 - Correspondence and agreements between Lodge 38 and Erie Division of New York Central, 1929-1943 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    Correspondence, manuscript. 1929-1933, 1943
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 38 - New York Central, 1933-1937 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 39 - Union shop contract New York Central at Buffalo, 1951-1962 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 41 - Correspondence, 1921-1933 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    Correspondence. 1921, 1932-1933
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 47, 1929-1933 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    Correspondence. 1929, 1931, 1933
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 51 - Case regarding T.J. Roach, 1921-1923 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    Correspondence. 1921, 1923
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 51 - Correspondence, 1921-1944 (Box 68, Folder 35)
- Records of Local Lodges (51 and 110-168 and 413) (Box 69)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodges 51 and 110 - Dispute involving Saginaw-Bay City, 1928-1933 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    A-E. Correspondence. 1928, 1931-1933.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 55 - Agreement, bylaws of Lodge 55 (Switchmen's Union of North America, New York Central west of Buffalo), 1926-1934 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Pamphlet, correspondence. 1926, 1929, 1934
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 55 - Correspondence, schedule of rate of pay, agreement with New York Central, 1931-1941 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, pamphlet.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 55 - Miscellaneous material, 1933-1938 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    A-1 - D-1. Miscellaneous.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 55 - Case of R.J. Trommeter, 1938 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 55 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1941-1967 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 55 - Proposals to Third Quadrennial Convention, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 57 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1922 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 58 - Correspondence regarding requesting wage increase, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 61 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1921 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 66 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1928-1944 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Record of Local Lodges: Lodge 67 - Correspondence on Grand Blanc Yard, 1942-1945 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 70 - Telegram, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 71 - Form letters, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 74 - records of local, 1921-1932 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 75 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1933-1943 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    Correspondence.1933, 1943
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 79 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1922-1943 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 80 - Local Business of Lodge 80, 1920-1938 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 80 - Correspondence regarding 26-day month, 1934-1935 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 80 - Correspondence regarding C. Bradley, A. Norris about controversy on payment of lodge bills, 1938-1943 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    Correspondence. 1938, 1943
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 83 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1921-1923 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodges 90 and 92 - Miscellaneous, 1943-1965 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1965
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 95 - Local lodge files, 1922-1944 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 95 - Cancellation of agreement regarding Ashtabula, 1937 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 95 - Claims and correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 102 - Circulation of ballots, 1943-1957 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1957
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 107 - Correspondence, financial statements, 1943-1968 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1953, 1957, 1968
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 110 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1923-1929 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 110 - Correspondence regarding Pere Marquette Railroad, 1931-1936 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 110 - Local minutes of meeting at Grand Rapids (Pere Marquette), 1937-1941 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    Correspondence. 1937, 1941
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 110 - General Grievance Committee meeting (Pere Marquette), 1945 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 110 - Revision of contract, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 116 - Correspondence, copy of agreement (Eastern, Western, Southeastern; 5 brotherhoods), 1943-1964 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1964
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 122 - Miscellaneous, 1923-1939 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 129 - Scranton Switchtender Case, bylaws, 1953-1955 (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodges 133, 137, 139, 1943-1961 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    Correspondence, manuscript. 1943, 1961
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 141 - Proposals to Switchmen's Union of North America convention, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 145, 147, 1943-1962 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1954, 1962
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 151 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1921-1952 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodges 157, 158 - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1943-1968 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1955, 1968
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 160 - Correspondence, agreement (Pere Marquette), 1932-1933 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    Correspondence, manuscript. 1932-1933
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 160 - Correspondence, agreement (Pere Marquette), 1916-1931 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    Correspondence, manuscript. 1916, 1925-1931.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 160 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1934-1946 (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 164 - The Snake Fang, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodges 168 and 413 - Report of third regional meeting, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 45)
- Records of Local Lodges (174-292) (Box 70)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 174 - Local Correspondence, 1943-1965 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1965.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 175 - Audit of their books, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 178 - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1919-1939 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 178 - Time claims correspondence, 1941-1944 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodges 185 and 187 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1924-1943 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Correspondence. 1924-1941, 1943
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 193 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodges 195 and 198 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1937-1956 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Correspondence. 1937, 1956
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 199 - Routine letters, 1924-1946 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 210 - Local Correspondence, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 212 - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding Pacific Naval Air Base and switching, 1944 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 213 - Local business, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 214 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1929-1944 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 214 - Local correspondence, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 215 - Local Correspondence, 1920-1937 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 218 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1943 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 230 - Miscellaneous, 1919 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 237 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1922-1946 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 243 - Correspondence regarding Los Angeles Junction Railway, 1951-1956 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 246 - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 253 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1923 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 261 - Correspondence, 1943-1948 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1948
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 262 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    Correspondence. 1955, 1957.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 263 - Correspondence regarding resolution, 1943-1946 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 2644 - Benefits of the lodge, 1951-1967 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    Correspondence. 1951, 1967
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 270 - Union shop citation members, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 277 - Local correspondence, 1936-1944 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 287 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1944-1955 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 291 - Miscellaneous claims paid to lodge members, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Records of Local Lodges - Lodge 294 - Miscellaneous, 1932-1956 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 295 - Miscellaneous, 1942-1944 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Cleveland Union Terminal Agreement, 1929 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Original and duplicate papers to form 299, 1930 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Minutes, 1930 (Box 70, Folder 33)
    13a. Bound volume. Manuscript.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Working papers, 1930 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Correspondence, rules of relief, agreement with Cleveland Union Terminal, 1931-1934 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1935-1939 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Suspension of H.C. Danielson for violations of Switchmen's Union of North America constitution, 1940-1941 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - H.C. Danielson versus M.E. Brown, P. O'Connor, C.M. Debow controversy, 1940-1942 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 265 - Minutes of meetings, 1926-1953 (Box 70, Folder 39)
    18a. Bound volume. Manuscript.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 292 - Membership and finance records, 1951-1954 (Box 70, Folder 40)
    18b. Bound volume. Manuscript.
- Records of Local Lodges (299-927); Correspondence between locals; General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence with Locals 1-10 (Box 71)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Miscellaneous business correspondence (Ferguson), 1940-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Correspondence on Danielson suspension, 1941-1942 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    2a. Bound volume. Minutes.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Check book for lodge, 1941-1944 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Bound volume. Receipt book.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Miscellaneous correspondence, agreement, relief fund, 1942 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Correspondence regarding Ferguson, 1947-1957 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Death of E. Henderson, 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    6a. Correspondence, news clippings, etcetera.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Union shop agreement, correspondence, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Ferguson correspondence regarding Cleveland Union Terminal, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Membership list, 1930-1931 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    8a. Bound volume.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Inauguration meeting, 1930-1942 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    8b. Bound volume, manuscript.
  - Records of Local Lodges: Lodge 299 - Membership and finance records, 1932-1935 (Box 71, Folder 13)